{
    "subject": "resource/Joaquin_Phoenix",
    "predicate": "property/relatives",
    "object": "resource/Liberty_Phoenix",
    "human_readable": "Joaquin Phoenix's relative is Liberty Phoenix.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9838923215866089,
            "question": "Is Joaquin Phoenix related to Liberty Phoenix?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9313305616378784,
            "question": "Name a relative of Joaquin Phoenix."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9262672662734985,
            "question": "Is there a family connection between Joaquin Phoenix and Liberty Phoenix?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9047840237617493,
            "question": "Who are some relatives of Joaquin Phoenix?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9007517099380493,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Joaquin Phoenix and Liberty Phoenix?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8814137578010559,
            "question": "Are Joaquin Phoenix and Liberty Phoenix siblings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8196672797203064,
            "question": "What is the name of one of Joaquin Phoenix's relatives?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7931033372879028,
            "question": "Who is Liberty Phoenix related to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7645323276519775,
            "question": "Do Joaquin Phoenix and Liberty Phoenix share any familial ties?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4924379289150238,
            "question": "Can you tell me about any family members of Joaquin Phoenix?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Joaquin Phoenix's relative is Liberty Phoenix.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5888_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do Joaquin Phoenix and Liberty Phoenix share any familial ties?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5888_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Liberty Phoenix related to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5888_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of one of Joaquin Phoenix's relatives?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5888_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5888_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5888_132.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5888_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5888_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5888_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5888_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5888_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5888_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5888_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5888_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that according to the documents, Joaquin Phoenix has siblings named River, Rain, Liberty, and Summer, with Liberty being one of them. This information supports the triple that Liberty Phoenix is a relative of Joaquin Phoenix."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the siblings of Joaquin Phoenix, including Liberty Phoenix. Therefore, it supports the statement that Joaquin Phoenix's relative is Liberty Phoenix."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}